<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gijs Nijholt - Solo Developer &amp; UI Engineer</title>
    <link>http://gijs.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gijs Nijholt - Solo Developer &amp; UI Engineer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://gijs.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Currently</title>
      <link>http://gijs.github.io/2021/10/currently/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 15:25:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gijs.github.io/2021/10/currently/</guid>
      <description>Side projects that I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on.
HelemaalGroen HelemaalGroen is a web application founded by Jaap de Boer, a retired veterinarian, who came up with the concept after being forced to walk instead of cycle after a cycling accident.
While walking, he noticed the large amounts of litter in the streets and decided to make a website to help people find and clean up litter.
The concept is to allow people to use a smartphone while they clean up litter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recently</title>
      <link>http://gijs.github.io/2021/10/recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 15:25:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gijs.github.io/2021/10/recently/</guid>
      <description>Interesting things I&amp;rsquo;ve stumbled upon recently.
Web dev &amp;amp; User interface   https://htmx.org/ - I&amp;rsquo;ve seen a bit too many hours get wasted fixing webpack configurations, so I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to using something like HTMX or Elixir LiveView to simplify some of my upcoming web UI work.
  Smartcrop.js: Node &amp;amp; browser smart cropping library
  Stitches: CSS-in-JS library with near-zero runtime, SSR, multi-variant support
  Theatre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World!</title>
      <link>http://gijs.github.io/2021/10/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 15:25:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gijs.github.io/2021/10/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>After writing on a regular basis between 2005 and 2018, I found myself spending more time on Twitter. But more so as a consumer than as a writer.
Perhaps I didn&amp;rsquo;t write much because of the character limit, but the real reason is probably that everything is directly pushed to followers.
A blog feels more calm to me. I don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about the content being too long, I can just write it and let the audience decide what to read.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
